(panting)
(Raj:)How you feeling?
(Penny:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Little claustrophobic.
(Raj:)Let's set up
the equipment.
(Raj:)It'll help take
your mind off of it.
(Sheldon:)Miners often sang mining songs
to keep their spirits up.
(Raj:)Do you know any
mining songs?
(Sheldon:)Just the hits.
♪ Where it's dark
as a dungeon ♪
♪ And it's damp
as the dew ♪
(Rajj:)That's pretty.
♪ Where the dangers
are double ♪
♪ And the pleasures
are few ♪
♪ Where the rain never falls ♪
♪ And the sun never shines ♪
♪ Yes, it's dark as a dungeon ♪
♪ Way down
in the mine ♪
(Raj:)It's a little more
bleak than I thought.
♪ Well, I pray
when I dead ♪
♪ And the ages shall roll ♪
♪ That my body will blacken ♪
♪ And turn into coal ♪
(Raj:)Getting kind
of grim.